<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>o_0</title>
    <description>A place to write some ramblings</description>
    <link>https://o-0.ooo/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://o-0.ooo/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:46:07 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:46:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Putting pen to paper</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lost in the rhythm of typing, I’ve always found a joy in writing. &lt;em&gt;Tappy&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;tap&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;tap&lt;/em&gt;. But always for an audience of one… &lt;strong&gt;me&lt;/strong&gt;. Now, though still hesitant to fully embrase my “authentic-self”, I am taking small steps toward inviting you into my world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BEHIND THE STORY:&lt;/strong&gt; This is an exploration of finding my voice amidst hesitation, a journey that inspires others to pursue authenticity in their own expressions.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to be honest with you, I’m still trying to find my voice at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, that sounds funny to say out loud – as I’m often found tapping away at my keyboard most hours of most days. Happy. Content. Mind wandering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But for the past few years I’ve been writing for an audience of one, me. I haven’t published anything online. I guess this is due to a mixture of me being busy, not &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wanting to show my authentic-self to the world, and not knowing what I’d want from opening up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for now I’m going to keep writing for an audience of one, but I’ll place the notebook on a table for others to stumble upon. Maybe over time I can get some feedback to help me on my search for my authentic voice, finding what resonates.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://o-0.ooo/articles/23/putting-pen-to-paper/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://o-0.ooo/articles/23/putting-pen-to-paper/</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
